<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
<script/>
<script/>
<channel>
<title>BlockchainX Web Stories</title>
<description>Get updated about blockchain with BlockchainX Web Stories - Blockchain Development Company. </description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories</link>
<image>
<url>https://www.blockchainx.tech/images/fav/fav1.png</url>
<title>BlockchainX Blog</title>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories</link>
</image>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2023 10:30:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<language> en </language>



<item>
<title>Decentralization Predicts and Shapes the Future of IoT</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;" />
<div>Most networking technologies lack the efficiency and performance needed to connect devices that are spread over large areas. The decentralized apps help to break the boundaries of device control, and connectivity issues for Internet-ready connected devices are no longer an obstacle.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/decentralization-predict-future-iot</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">90ec8d45844c4a6aa0c3d7dd3c9a5805</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Factors leading to the success of NFT Marketplace</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;" />
<div>The gaining popularity of NFT leads to the emergence of many NFT marketplaces and a question arises – how to make an NFT marketplace successful? It is important to consider market demand, platform features, technology stack, security, user experience, legal compliance, payment processing, marketing and promotion, and ongoing maintenance and support.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/reasonable-factors-success-nft-marketplace</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2445e474658942ffbf4999490da2b131</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
<title>6 Potential Use Cases and Examples of the Metaverse for Businesses</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;" />
<div>Unlock the potential of the metaverse with our exploration of the top 6 real-world use cases and examples. So get ready to dive into this post to get captivating examples &amp; use cases that will help you discover the transformative potential of the metaverse across various industries.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/six-real-world-use-cases-examples-metaverse</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">e7b3985f62674073ad9e70acdd94c64c</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg" />
</item>

<item>
<title>Social Token - Better way to brand your Brand</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Want to get social in the crypto-verse Looking for new ways to capture audience and community with added benefits Create your Social token with Blockchain and make the web3 enthusiasts turn in as your community members</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/rise-of-social-token</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">d97352e8fb664a04bcacfe4edf6c9fa3</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>Permissioned Blockchain - What is It capable of</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>The benefits of creating a permissioned blockchain is wider. Choosing to develop one for your business contribute in efficient management and takes control on everything as one with custom privacy and what more BlockchainX can help you with better inputs in developing your Permissioned blockchain, connect now</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/create-permissioned-blockchain</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">f50ef673d1724a2a9fe31dcdfe72f7e4</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>Create your own NFT Marketplace on Polygon</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Launch your own NFT Marketplace on Polygon with a fast, low-cost, and eco-friendly blockchain network and start selling unique digital assets today</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/create-nft-marketplace-polygon</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">24810e011e204113ad7b2acb6de93dee</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>AI in Web3 games and the Metaverse</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>The potential for AI is limitless, and we're eager to explore what the future holds for this amazing technology in the ever-changing world of Web3 and the Metaverse.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/artificial-intelligence-into-web3-games-metaverse</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">24c9a5ea9792439ca9aa453604d889d0</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>Everything you need to know about the new revolution in digital identities</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Users and organizations no longer need to rely on third-party services for identity verification. The benefits of decentralized identities open a new era of seamless and interoperable access to the Internet. Learn more about decentralized identity through this post.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/decentralization-emphasizes-digital-identity-management</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">9a3c30270c194277a1eb26ba3b91497d</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>AI and Blockchain Join Hands to Raise the Modern Transportation System</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>The use of Blockchain and AI technologies has the potential to bridge technology gaps in transportation systems, and this is a tremendous growth that has fueled the transformation of the transportation industry.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/ai-and-blockchain-transportation-to-next-level</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">8d9b07faf41244d2ab315c5e5238c171</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>Impact of AI and Blockchain on Mordern Finance</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>The impact of AI and Blockchain on financial services is substaintial and we can expect continued growth and innovation in this area. The future of financial services will be more secure, efficent and customer-centric in the hands of AI and Blockchain</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/ai-and-blockchain-meet-finance</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">92863dbe496d401ba37f2394205b006e</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>AI and blockchain in creativity</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>The transformational change brought about by AI and blockchain will enrich our lives with more personal, creative, and abstract experiences. The tokenization of digital assets leads to a flourishing of creativity and innovation as individuals and communities come together to build entirely new worlds and experiences.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/ai-and-blockchain-in-creativity</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">e0188fc99956431eb68ca70be39ee7a6</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>Blockchain in Supply Chain - Entacting Traceability and Transparency Together</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>With the need to handle big data and breed through complex transactions of Supply chain, Blockchain integration in one effective solution. Explore there combined abilities in here!</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/blockchainx-in-supply-chain-management</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">20622a64c3bc45f2b488eb3c9f63fb3a</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>What do AI and Blockchain Technology Think About the Modern Sports Industry</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>With recent developments in professional sports analytics, the adoption of AI and blockchain in sports has become increasingly important. Artificial intelligence and blockchain technology are completely changing the way sports are consumed and analyzed, from athletes, advertisers, and broadcasters to viewers. Let's see how it is.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/how-can-ai-and-blockchain-redefine-sports</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">9b1a42d9eeea45b1ac86b689963f23dc</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>The impact of AI and Blockchain Technology on Education</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>These two cutting-edge technologies enhance personalized and interactive learning for students. Textbooks have been replaced with media-centric content, helping students gain better knowledge and learning experience, where AI and Blockchain technology works amazingly.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/what-happens-when-education-meets-ai-and-blockchain</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">276b1a353f8543a1a99fefbcd625698b</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>NFT Marketplace - Stiff and Sturdy NFT Platform On Avalanche Network</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Are you a creator with ideas blowing the world? Here with BlockchainX and by availing our services you can develop your Creative economy and erect your community in the web3 market with our NFT marketplace on Avalanche development. Customized solution based on your needs and business requirement, contact now to grab more insights.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/create-your-nft-marketplace-on-avalanche</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">96f47f280b334faf8925c29cf3121b84</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>Solana NFT Marketplace - Develop Your Powerpacked NFT Platform With BlockchainX</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Solana blockchain network is considered efficient in terms of making quick transactions. Read through this blog, to understand how effective is its to build an NFT marketplace in Solana. Catch up here!</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/nft-marketplace-development-solana</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">24c250503b924f29897d3c6668ff8c63</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>How to create your own Metaverse virtual world</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>If you want to be a part of the internet of the future, you should consider building  a metaverse, and this blog will explain how to build a metaverse world.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/how-to-create-your-own-Metaverse-virtual-world</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">e0e2fe561d3d4908acbe8a9a5b77f7cd</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>NFT Marketplace Development - Customized Decentralised Platform Solution</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Invest in our capabilities, get to launch a fully functional, decentralized and highly efficient solution. By choosing us as your NFT marketplace development partner we can ensure you render a qualified and quantified platform with customized abilities and functionals. </div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/how-to-create-an-nft-marketplace</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">5134d3ac791b4a0a99ed779fef944de0</guid>
<title>NFTs, the sensation that overcame the the stigma of crypto “Hype”: Past, Present, and Future</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Anyone who knows about NFTs and the world of blockchain will be eager to know about the future of nft. In this article, you can understand the possible future for nft and the challenges of the non fungible token. Read on to know more.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/future-nft-applications-challenges</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">5d7c25d9db5946e889c468704e15271f</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>NFTs And Their Role In The Metaverse</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>NFTs and Metaverse are closely related and can help us create whole new digital economies. Development of metaverse and nft are highly in demand. This is why.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/nfts-and-their-role-in-the-metaverse</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">217cd9990f204ea28f7f17c95cb5a5fd</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>NFT Marketplace: Everything You Need To Know</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Many people wonder, why do you need an NFT marketplace, and who is it for? In this blog, you’ll learn the possibilities of these platforms and how to create an NFT marketplace. Read on to know more.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/nft-marketplace-everything-you-need-to-know</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">85278a617076449186ed9987b67f4b46</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>How are NFTs used In DeFi - Decentralized Finance</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>NFTs and DeFi are closely related and have a lot to offer. Using NFTs in Decentralized finance opens doors to endless possibilities. Read on to find out how.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/how-are-nfts-used-in-defi</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">8091107775e44930a88c21efe79d4eb7</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>blockchain and ai : coming to intersect in the metaverse</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Artificial intelligence and blockchain technology are being combined in the metaverse. This blog discusses how the blockchain metaverse and the AI metaverse meet to impact the metaverse world.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/blockchain-role-ai-meet-the-world-metaverse</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">08c24b989ea84d03a93540896871b7b3</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Future of the Metaverse: Is it Hype, Hope, or Hell? | BlockchainX</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>There is a lot of buzz going around the internet right now about the metaverse and how big a deal it is that the internet's blockchain technology will grow over the next few years. A lot of people talk about how this is a massive trend and a huge game changer, but what exactly is the metaverse? Why is it such a big deal? What are people using it for ? This blog will help you to know the future of the metaverse. Read in depth</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/the-future-of-metaverse</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">994e993c97e8435c80f207e696f5c488</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>Are NFTs a gimmick or the Future of Gaming? — NFTs in the gaming world | BlockchainX</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>NFTs have been intensifying to have a significant impact on gaming businesses.Since video games are virtual, they are an ideal sector for vital marketplaces to flourish and add value. But is there any benefit to having the future of NFTs in the gaming world? Let's view this blog in depth.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/nft-gimmick-or-feature-of-gaming</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">95311e2fdd6041ce8e41a0ff17add788</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>Top 5 Metaverse Projects to keep on your radar in 2022</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Learn the Reason to Invest in Bitcoin on 2021 and know more about the investment advice, why bitcoin get more traction, why bitcoin is a good investment and benefits in bitcoin.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/top-5-metaverse-projects</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">45d097981cd445c99b9752c795a00b27</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>Things you need to know about the innovative world: The Metaverse Keynotes.</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Many of us may think of Metaverse as a fascinating thing, but at the same time, enterprises must prepare for this metaverse technology, strengthen blockchain capabilities, protect against metaverse and security risks, and embrace a new way of the Internet. To do that, we need to understand the key features of the metaverse.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/know-the-key-features-of-metaverse</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">ced2ec14e5a34e19bbec26b52d38a117</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Top Nine Insightful Things to Consider Before Starting with NFT Marketplace development</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Would you like to start developing your NFT marketplace? Before you launch it, consider these insightful things. This will help you in your NFT Marketplace development quickly and provide high-quality solutions. Now let's dive deeper to explore tem.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/nft-market-place-insights</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">cfd416ecb8f747fdad272789cc49ec46</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Major Blockchain Platforms to look for in 2023</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Blockchain technology appears to be speedy nowadays. So we have made a list of the major blockchain platforms that you can explore in 2023 to assist organizations in bringing more transparency and efficiency into their business ecosystems using blockchain.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/top-blockchain-platforms-explore-in-2023</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">330c841437784172a2e43efb11cb8c73</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Is Web3 shaping the future internet?: Know the latest trends of Web 3</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Web 3.0 is the future internet. Day-2-Day meta world came up with the latest trends and Web3 upgrades with these trends. Read this post to catch this trend at the right time.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/everything-you-need-to-know-about-web3</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">41af494ef0fd4f8a88df002c2d2b622f</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Why NFTs and what are their benefits?</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Let's take a look at the uses and benefits of NFTs in the virtual world of metaverse and blockchain technology.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/advantages-of-nft</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">b0243e06094e495ba383b43220d927a2</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mistakes you shouldn't do but know about it in the NFT Marketplace | BlockchainX
 </title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>If you have the desire to create an NFT marketplace, you will most likely need adequate study, preparation, and some initial investment to make your project more successful. Here we point out some mistakes you should avoid when building your NFT marketplace.
</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/6-mistakes-you-should-avoid-developing-nft-marketplace</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">7380a32184a44c3889be36a036a57497</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Best DeFi Platforms - A Brief Look On Decentralized Finance Platforms Before 2023 | BlockchainX
</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Having a great confusion on which Defi Platform is right? Here are a few norms and checklists that you need to leap on before 2023 for listing your projects on DeFi Platforms. To get a full view to yield better investments read through the whole blog.
</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/best-defi-platforms-to-consider-before-entering-2023</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">184da3dee3f84a7b88ec3f7b65bc5fa6</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>DeFi vs CeFi : What are they and which one is suitable for your business
 </title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>When it comes to buying and storing your hard-earned cryptocurrencies and crypto assets, you will be faced with a choice: CeFi(centralized finance) vs DeFi (decentralized finance). From this blog , you can decide which is better for you
</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/defi-vs-cefi</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6ded1503a06440d7abb3c3d637d2fd6a</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Everything about the Metaverse NFT Marketplace
 </title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Making a Metaverse NFT marketplace with unique and interesting features will entice a large number of users. With the well-known NFT marketplace, you can take your business to the next level.
</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/everything-about-nft-metaverse</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">72969445-47c1430cb7a36512298d67ae</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>What is Stellar Consensus Protocol and its benefits </title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Make blockchain payments with high speed and security through Stellar Consensus Protocol. </div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/stellar-consensus-protocol</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">a77e281233344b5ba920d7b5f7ce4b73</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>What is NFT Staking and How to Earn Income From NFTs </title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>It is not enough to buy NFTs, you have to earn income from them. NFT staking is like DeFi yield farming. You can make money from staking by owning such assets. Not only can you tokenize your assets but also earn money using them. In this article, we cover everything you need to know about NFT staking and how to make use of NFTs. </div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/what-is-nft-staking</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">e2484a4a6c8d41c2927fd9c9caae8d64</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Metaverse In Real Estate - Real Escape Space That You Can Build With Our Extensive Web3 Expertise.   </title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>Web3 is something that came in the GenZ but everyone and anyone would obviously want to explore. And  if you want to catch up and understand on the hookword Real Estate Metaverse, read the blog to gain more information and build your space in it. </div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/metaverse-in-real-estate</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">5fb911a9537242168b3e843f026c3051</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Metaverse Use Cases And Benefits - All The You Need To Know About Metaverse Benefits In Digital Era </title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>The most approachable and customized platform, Metaverse use cases are wide and vast, alongside the benefits of the metaverse is also valuable. This opens an arena to explore the potential of both individual games and team play. Explore the various applications of the metaverse here. </div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/metaverse-use-case-benefits</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">04fe4eca2f9646c4bd3d049375227cd3</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>How to Create your own NFT Marketplace in 2023</title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.jpg" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>The profit-making NFT marketplace is touching the heights of success through its features. Until now and then (2023) this futuristic market place grabs human minds.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/how-to-create-your-own-nft-marketplace-in-2023</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">65b862b423da4ed3b239c4b50eb68331</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.jpg"/>
</item>
<item>
<title> DAO - What does Decentralised Automated Organizations Hold For Future?
 </title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.png" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>The global transition over digitalization and decentralization have brought huge impact that’s foreseen to have admirable capacity in the following era. While DAOs that are emerging today are kneeling strong on the motive to hold an undeniable role in the space. Check out more on that.</div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/dao-in-nft</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">1c13d010bf19426f87c1fffadf05d319</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.png"/>
</item>
<item>
<title> ISO 20022 - Highly influential aspect of Crypto industry | BlockchiainX
 </title>
<description>
<div>
<img src="assets/1.png" style="width: 100%;"/>
<div>ISO 20022 is considered one of the influential factor of Crypto industry, but do you know what is cheating such impact and how its done? Tap on and slide left to know in detail on ISO 20022. </div>
</div>
</description>
<link>https://www.blockchainx.tech/web-stories/what-is-iso-20022</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">13bbfe5b006b4d85a23e16d0eb83049f</guid>
<dc:creator> BlockchainX </dc:creator>
<media:content medium="image" url="assets/1.png"/>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
